Well then, Playboy!
Nice petch!
Ready?
Wow!
Yes, so today is a special opening and closing ceremony for Orix
We're here at the Night Sky Room!
Oh no!
I'm so nervous!
Isn't it terrible to stand in front of this thing?
On top of this dungeon.
Look at these uniforms.
Ta-da!
Oh, man.
Everyone put in their favorite number.
You can put your name on it.
And they made them.
It's so cool.
It's really cool.
And everyone gets a number.
They gave me the number I wanted.
So, who's going to throw today?
I wonder who it is.
Uh-oh.
Ta-da!
It's me.
I knew it.
It's just...
I never get to do a special opening ceremony like this.
I'll never get to do it.
I really want to make it a thing.I really want to make it a thing.
And I want to throw it so that I can reach it properly.
I want to make sure it reaches the target.
Straight ahead.
Please let us know how you feel.
I'll do my best.
I'll see you later.
I'm off.
Magic Oroko. Hey!
Operate Operate ah Operate
Where's Ayanan's curry?
Rose.
It's a catch-all ball.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
Ayanan's curry?
Here!
My signature ball.
I'm a southpaw.
I'm getting nervous.
I'm getting nervous. My skin is getting dry.
I don't care.
Oh, no! I want to put sand cream on it.
Go for it, go for it!
But you're here.
I've been getting a lot of mail.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
It's so beautiful.
Thank you for watching.Thank you for watching!
Oh!
Our center direction is
I don't know if it's natural or not.
I'd be afraid of someone throwing it just behind me or something.
That's true. This is the only problem.
I'm worried.
Okay, let's go.
Okay?
Cool.
Please listen to the announcer play the ball before you throw it.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
That's totally fine.
We're gonna die.
What? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. We're coming to America.
But it's so cool, isn't it?
I'm too nervous to say anything.
But I hope it'll be fun.
It's a special conductor's room.
I don't think I'll ever have a chance to do that.
I'm going to cherish it.
I'm going to make the most of it.
I'd like to throw the ball so that it reaches the audience.
Good luck.
You'll pitch as usual?
As usual.
Behind you, next to you.
I've lost the sound of volleyball.I lost my volleyball sound.
Cute.
Amazing!
Sounds great!
It's funny when you throw it a little bit!
It hurts!
Ouch!
Subscribe to our channel!
The new SR Cliender design itself is also on display, so it's hard to find a new store with as many sonementum numbers as we have.
And now, we will have a special designated game!
Today's special participants are all members of the Starlust Perfection girl group, Aven Plus.
Today we will have AIDA-san representing DUEMO.
Our staff is Oda, and our catcher is Ishikawa. Please do so.
To start, the scatcher, Aven Plus, AIDA!
Bouncer, Oda, Scatcher, Ishikawa, Sorgun, Playbo!
Please wait for severe hot water!
Daikichi
It was really like a little bit just before and at home,
I really thought it was definitely not going to work today.
I wanted to practice more,
I practiced with the catcher before the game,
I managed to throw the ball,
It was a miracle.
In my rehearsal, I was like, "Straight up, bang! I was really like a professional baseball player.
I imagined that I was really like a professional baseball player. I always imagined that I was really as good as a professional baseball player.
I wonder if I could do that? Could I do it?
Next, we will make a new presentation.
We're going to make today's game EXTREMELY LIGHT!
So, please come on over.
Extreme Torso, Mr. President.
Did you say play ball?
He said it.
Did he say it?
Oh, thank God.
It's over.
Afrotto, Otsuka, and Hirose will be presented with a new one.
Nervous?
Thank you for watching.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
What's that? That? That one?
One more time. One more time.
One more time.
Do you want to do it one more time?
Confirmation.
That's it.
Let's do it.
Let's see if we can do it. Can we do it?
Confirmed.
Let's go.
Let's see if we can do it.
Aim for the next staff member.
He said he failed.
Even if you only complete the easy games.
Okay, okay.
I did it.
It's perfect.
Thank you very much.
I did it before I checked.
I'm sorry.
Three, two, one.
[ED]
I started the story activity for January 20.
Tired of being busy one
speeding from downtown
Venue enjoys going home
Laughing
magnifying glass
Confused
I'd like to have a drink with you.
I'd like to try my hand at producing a player
Oh no, I'm curious
I got taken on a snow bounce.
Oh, roulette par!
Okay, today's challenge is for you, sister.
Let's go. Roulette-per-code.
Now, please put on your bells and vertellies.Now, please put on your bells and vertellies!
Half a heart, right hand, oh, that way, that way, and the rest, yum!
Oh, that smile, that smile, keep it, please.
Okay, let's go with the smile.
Transformation time begins!
Here come the beautiful Arts.
Cute.
Do more.
All the members of Arts are here,
Arts, and Masayoshi Oda is here with all of us.
Let's give a big round of applause to all of you right away.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
Few foo foo.
I want to eat something sweet, but it's very gutsy,
I'll do that. But the one called Ikekara looks really good.
I'm an idol, and you're Squeeze-kun.
Squeeze!
Please learn it.
There are so many places that entertain me.
Food is one of them,
Pictures of the players?
I enjoy walking around,
It was fun to walk around.
I hope we will be able to play live in a big place someday,When we perform in a big venue someday, we would like to incorporate various aspects of that kind of thing,
I would like to incorporate various aspects like that into our live performances.
Like making hearts like that,
And also making pot stops like that.
Maybe someday we can make a new video for AmeFlash.
Maybe some roots where you can watch funny videos.
Absolutely not!
I don't like that one bit.
Do something crazy and weird that people will draw up.
Just my own stuff.
I have so much of everyone's stuff.
Please don't do that.
We also wanted to do a food collaboration with the players.
I ate a lot of food.
It was delicious.
It was a lot of fun.
I hope you will invite us again,
We will incorporate the lyrics of the next season,
We look forward to working with you.
Helping out.
Awesome.
Nice touch of aframoy.
I heard that this bill can be a bill if we have a concert here.
I want to do it!
Why don't you do handprints of those who gave concerts here?
Like that?
That kind of thing?
What kind of handprints?
Bruno Month!
There were handprints of all kinds of famous people, There were handprints from various famous people,
Let's definitely do it someday!
It's like the person who gives the concert can do it.
I was so excited before.
But I love it when Bruno Mance and Missy from Black Pink do a lot too!
I want to do this side by side.
I want to do it!
I heard Momokuro-san did it too,
I wanted to do a live concert for my senpai.
I'll try my best to make it so I can do a concert.
Keep up the good work!
Bon appétit!
I was really nervous.
When I was practicing, I was a little closer to the audience.
I was a little closer to the person who was going to touch me.
But when I stood there, it was farther than I thought,
We kept talking that it was too far.
But the members were supporting me behind,
I was able to throw with that feeling on my back, so I was happy about that.
It felt really good.
And it was good.
I caught it without even looking at it.
Really?
It was great.
I didn't hear any of that warbling.
I know it makes you nervous.
But you were warmly wowing me.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much for giving me this wonderful opportunity.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
It really simply has the lyrics You Can Do It,
I am really glad from the bottom of my heart.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much for watching it.
It's all thanks to you.
It's true.
The Oryx fans were so kind to me,
Even when I passed by them, they told me that they were doing it for me,
I thought they were very kind to me.
I was very happy.
It was warm, wasn't it?
I would love to meet you again.
I would like to go to Groom. Also.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.